testflightapp.com 2013-08-20

# TestFlight » Beta Testing On The Fly

* * *

TestFlight App Inc. (the “Company”, “we” or “us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from Developers and Beta Testers on [www.testflightapp.com](http://www.testflightapp.com/) (the “Website”) and from Users, Developers and Beta Testers through TestFlight or TestFlight Live (collectively, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies to information that is provided to us through the Website or that we receive through the Services. Our Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Website at [www.testflightapp.com/privacy](http://www.testflightapp.com/privacy). This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites, applications or services that display or link to different privacy statements. 

YOU ARE HEREBY ADVISED THAT YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, ANY APPLICABLE CURRENT AND PRIOR VERSIONS, AND ANY AMENDMENTS THERETO. 

  1. ###  Understanding the Services and types of users. 

The website provides two different types of services available to three types of user. 

    1. The first service is TestFlight which is available to App Developers (“Developers”) and beta testers (“Beta Testers”). Both the Developer and the Beta Tester must sign up at the Website to utilize this service. 

    2. The second service is TestFlight Live which is available to Developers and App users (“Users”). TestFlight Live allows Developers to receive real time analytics from Users so that Developers may improve App performance. A User does not sign up on the Website. 

Both services operate differently and are addressed separately where applicable in the sections below. 

  2. ###  Information Collection: 

Personally Identifiable Information that we collect from TestFlight’s Developers and Beta Testers through the Website. 

In the course of using the Website, Developers and Beta Testers may provide us with certain personally identifiable information. This refers to information about Developers and Beta Testers that can be used to contact or identify them, and information on their use of and activities at the Website that may be connected with them (“Website Personal Information”). Website Personal Information that we collect may include, but is not limited to, a Developer or Beta Tester’s name, telephone number, credit card details or other billing information, email address, home and business postal addresses, and Apple iOS Unique Device Identifier (UDID). Website Personal Information may also include information Developers or Beta Testers supply to us concerning their preferences and interests expressed in the course of use of the Website. 

When Developers or Beta Testers visit the Website to use the Service, our servers automatically record information that their browser or device provides to us. This information may include, but is not limited to, the Developer or Beta Tester’s computer or device’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page it was visiting before it came to the Website and information it searches for on the Website. Like many websites, we may also use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to the Developer or Beta Tester’s computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We may use “persistent cookies” to save the Developer or Beta Tester’s registration ID and login password for future logins to the Website; and we use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Website, to better understand how Developers and Beta Testers interact with the Website and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Website. The Developer or Beta Tester can instruct its browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt before accepting a cookie from the websites it visits. If the browser does not accept cookies, however, it may not be able to access all portions of the Website or all functionality of our services. 

When a Developer or Beta Tester uploads mobile applications (“App(s)”) to the Website, we may also record certain information related thereto, such as the number of times a Developer or Beta Tester installs an App, the number of Apps a Developer or Beta Tester has access to, the number of times a Developer or Beta Tester views an App’s description, and whether a Developer or Beta Tester tries to install an App without being authorized to. It is important to note that we cannot install a Developer’s App on our devices as each App is encrypted and protected and may only be opened by authorized devices. We also cannot access the release notes or other files packaged with a Developer’s App unless access is expressly granted by the Developer to us. Apps, IPAs, provisioning profiles and other application sensitive information remain the Developer’s property and shall not be part of the Website Personal Information. We make no claim to ownership of any Apps unless created and uploaded by us. 

Information we collect from TestFlight Live’s Users through the Service. 

Users of TestFlight Live do not sign up for the service, so to prevent an intrusion of privacy we have made an effort to minimize the amount of sensitive or identifiable data provided to us by the service. 

When a Developer includes the TestFlight Live SDK in an App, we receive certain “User Information” that will help the Developer improve the App experience. User Information is comprised of: timestamp, App version, User’s device name, device model, language, carrier, architecture, network state (i.e. wifi or cellular data), events, errors and the User’s last action in the App. The User Information also includes a device identifier, such as the handset’s UDID; however, this is immediately hidden and converted into a random, proprietary, non-traceable TestFlight ID viewable only to Company and not to the Developer. 

  3. ###  How We Use Personal Information 

How we use Website Personal Information from TestFlight 

Website Personal Information is or may be used for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve the Website, services, features and content, (ii) to administer a Developer or Beta Tester’s use of the Website, (iii) to enable a Developer or Beta Tester to enjoy and easily navigate the Website, (iv) to better understand a Developer or Beta Tester’s needs and interests, (v) to fulfill requests that a Developer or Beta Tester may make, (vi) to personalize a Developer or Beta Tester’s experience, (vii) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements, and (viii) to provide Developers or Beta Testers with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe they may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by us or third parties. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive any such communications, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of the communications sent to you, or update your “account settings” information. (See “Changing or Deleting Information” below). 

We use information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Website and our services, for the Website’s technical administration, to increase the Website’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to Developers or Beta Testers’ needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that visitors to the Website meet the criteria required to process their requests. 

How we use User Information in TestFlight Live 

User Information will be stored on our secure services and provided to Developers to help troubleshoot crashes, discover bugs and improve Apps. We will analyze the User Information and provide it to Developers in the form of performance metrics, error reporting and user utilization information. We may also aggregate the User Information for other reporting. We will not sell or expose the User Information to third parties. Although we take best efforts to protect User Information, we are not responsible for use by any Developers of any data about their Users. Users should review the Developer’s policies to understand their use of Users’ data. 

  4. ### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Whether acquired through TestFlight or TestFlight Live, the Company does not sell, rent or share Website Personal Information or User Information without the Developer, Beta Tester or User’s consent (as appropriate), except as follows: 

    1. _Developers and Beta Testers._ We will display Website Personal Information in each Developer and Beta Tester’s profile page and elsewhere on the Website according to the preferences set in each account. Any information a Developer or Beta Tester chooses to provide should reflect how much it wants other users to know about it. We recommend that each Developer or Beta Tester guard its anonymity and sensitive information, and we encourage Developers and Beta Testers to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. Developers and Beta Testers can review and revise their profile information at any time. 

    2. _Service Providers, Business Partners and Others._ We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Website-related services (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Website’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how the Website and Services are used. These third parties have access to your Website and User Personal Information solely for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf. We intend to make reasonable efforts to ensure that these third parties execute industry standard confidentiality agreements to protect Website and User Personal Information. 

    3. _Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement._ TestFlight cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any Website or User Personal Information to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of the Company or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. 

    4. Right to Reference. Unless you provide express written notice otherwise, the Company shall have the right to reference and refer to the usage of, and relationship with, you or your company, which may be determined by the domain used in your registered email account. No press releases shall be made without your written consent. 

    5. Business Transfers. The Company may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Website and User Personal Information, in connection with or in anticipation of a corporate event, including a merger, acquisition, sale of stock, recapitalization, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 

  5. ###  Changing or Deleting Website Personal Information provided in TestFlight 

A Developer or Beta Tester may review, update, correct or delete the Website Personal Information provided in its registration or account profile for TestFlight by changing its “account settings.” 

There is no personal information provided by the User in TestFlight Live, therefore this section is not applicable. 

  6. ###  Opting Out of TestFlight Live 

A User cannot opt out of TestFlight Live and the submission of User Information, except by deleting or uninstalling the App that contains TestFlight Live. Users should contact an App’s developer to determine if the App contains TestFlight Live. 

  7. ### Security

The Company is very concerned with safeguarding and protecting all Website Personally Information and User Information. We employ reasonable measures and security designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. These measures include encrypting sensitive information using a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and storing information behind a firewall. However, the Company cannot ensure, guarantee or warrant the security of all information held, especially against third party attacks or intrusions. Therefore all information provided to the Company is provided at the Developer, Beta Tester or User’s risk. 

  8. ###  Transfer of Information 

If you are not a resident of the United States, you understand and agree that the Company stores and processes your information on computers located in the United States, and by providing any data to the Company, you consent to the transfer of such information to the United States and the application of the laws of the United States. 

  9. ### Our Policy Toward Children

This Website is not directed to children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Website Personal Information or User Information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Website Personal Information or User Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@testflightapp.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Website Personal Information or User Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

* * *

This User Privacy Policy describes how TestFlight App, Inc. (“FlightPath”) collects, users and discloses information we receive from end users (“users”) of mobile applications (“applications” or “apps”) that incorporate the FlightPath service. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will post the new Privacy Policy at www.testflightapp.com/privacy. 

When we say “you” (or similar pronouns) below, we are referring to users. If you want information about how FlightPath collects, uses and discloses information about developers who use FlightPath, please click here.

YOUR USE OF ANY DEVELOPER APP USING FLIGHTPATH CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

  1. ### User Information.

FlightPath does not collect personally identifiable user information – we will never request your name, email address, or other information that could be used to contact you or identify you personally. When we say “User Information” we mean the version of the app you are using, your device name, device model, device identifier (e.g., advertiser ID, publisher ID, UDID or MAC address) language, carrier, architecture, network state (i.e. wifi or cellular data), events, errors, IP address and various engagement data (ie. how long the app was in use, how often the app is used, if the user has reached various checkpoints in the app as defined by the developer, etc.). In the case of UDIDs and MAC addresses, this is immediately converted into a random, proprietary, non-traceable FlightPath ID viewable only to FlightPath and not to the developer.

  2. ### Opting Out. 

If you want to opt out of FlightPath collection of user information, please send your UDID and MAC address to optout@flightpathapp.com.

  3. ### How We Use Information

    1. FlightPath provides the user information it gathers to developers. Developers use this information in many ways: to understand how users interact with their apps, which helps them improve the user experience and offer relevant ads, to troubleshoot crashes, discover bugs, improve apps, provide in app notifications to users and contribute to the quality of products and services they offer.
    2. In addition to providing raw user data, FlightPath analyzes user information and provides developers with information such as performance metrics, error reporting and user utilization information.
    3. While FlightPath does not collect personally identifiable information from users, we do not control whether developers may combine the information we provide them with other information gathered by the developer, such as your registration information. FlightPath is not responsible for how developers use data about their users – you should review the developer’s policies to understand their use of users’ data. In addition, we may share your information with our corporate parent, provided that our parent company will use such information only within the scope of this Privacy Policy.
  4. ### Information Sharing and Disclosure

As described above, FlightPath does not collect personally identifiable user information. Of the limited information that FlightPath does collect, we will share user information with developers (as described above). We will not share user information with marketers, although we may help determine which marketer’s ads are more relevant to you. We may also share user information as follows: 

    1. Our Service Providers. If we use outside companies to provide all or part of the FlightPath Services on our behalf (for example, data storage, maintenance, database management, analytics and payment processing), these third parties will have access to user information solely to perform these tasks on our behalf. We will bind these companies to confidentiality terms that are consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    2. Legal Compliance. FlightPath cooperates with government officials, law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose user information to government officials, law enforcement officials and private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.
    3. Business Transfers. FlightPath may share, transfer or sell some or all of its assets, including user information, in connection with or in anticipation of a corporate event, including a merger, acquisition, sale of stock, recapitalization, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.
  5. ### Transfer of Information to United States and Elsewhere

FlightPath stores and processes user information on computers located in the United States and and may also store and process user information in other countries both within and outside the European Union. By using an app that uses FlightPath, you expressly consent to the transfer of the information described in this Privacy Policy to the United States and other countries within and outside the EU, and to the application of the laws of the United States.

  6. ### Our Policy Toward Children

The Website and our Services are not intended for children under 18 years of age and we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If you are aware that a child under 18 has signed up for a developer account or that a child under 13 is using an app that uses FlightPath or has provided us with information in some other way, please contact us at privacy@flightpathapp.com. 

  7. ### California Residents

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, also known as the “Shine the Light Law,” developers who are California residents are entitled to request and receive once a year, free of charge, a notice from us describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared, the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, and their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the contact address below. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response. 

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes how TestFlight App Inc. (“FlightPath”) collects, users and discloses information we receive from developers through use of www.flightpathapp.com (the “Website”) and the FlightPath services. We will refer to the Website and the FlightPath services collectively as the “Services”. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will notify you of updates by posting the new Privacy Policy at www.testflightapp.com/privacy. 

This Developer Privacy Policy covers “developers”, meaning the application developers who use FlightPath to understand how users interact with their mobile applications (“applications” or “apps”). If you want information about how FlightPath collects, uses and discloses information about end users and their interaction with the mobile apps using FlightPath, please click here. When we say “you” (or similar pronouns) below, we are referring to developers. 

YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE AND/OR THE SERVICES CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

  1. ### Your FlightPath Contract and Your User Privacy Policy.

    1. If your written agreement with FlightPath gives FlightPath broader rights than this Privacy Policy (for example, if the agreement gives FlightPath the right to use your name in its marketing materials), that written agreement is the governing document.
    2. You must prominently post your own legally sufficient privacy policy that informs your users that you are using the FlightPath service and that the FlightPath service will gather, use and disclose user information as described in our user privacy policy. 
  2. ### Account Information. 

When you activate a FlightPath developer account (including by keeping the TestFlight SDK in any app that you make publicly available), you give us certain information that may include you name, email address, telephone number, credit card or other billing information and physical address. We call this type of information “account information”. 
  3. ### Automated Information. 

When we say “automated information”, we mean any information about your use of the Services that is gathered automatically by our servers or by cookies or other technologies. When you visit the Website, our servers automatically record information such as your computer’s or device’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page the browser was viewing before it came to the Website and the information the browsers searches for on the Website. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Website; and we also use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Website, to better understand how developers interact with the Website and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Website. You can set your browser to stop accepting cookies or to ask you before accepting a cookie but you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website or our Services. 
  4. ### How We Use Information

We use account information and automated information for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve the Website, services, features and content, (ii) to administer your use of the Website, (iii) to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the Website, (iv) to better understand your needs and interests, (v) to fulfill your requests, (vi) to personalize your experience, (vii) to provide or offer updates and product announcements, and (viii) to provide you with information and offers that we believe you may find useful. In addition, we may share your information with our corporate parent, provided that our parent company will use such information only within the scope of this Privacy Policy. You can opt out of communications that are not related to your account by following the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of these communications or by updating your “account settings” information. (See “Changing Your Information” below.) 
  5. ### Information Disclosure

FlightPath does not sell, rent or share developer information without your consent except as follows: 
    1. Our Service Providers. If we use outside companies to provide all or part of the Services on our behalf (for example, data storage, maintenance, database management, analytics and payment processing), these third parties will have access to developer information solely to perform these tasks on our behalf. We will bind these companies to confidentiality terms that are consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    2. Legal Compliance. FlightPath cooperates with government officials, law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose developer information to government officials, law enforcement officials and private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.
    3. Right to Reference. Unless your written agreement with FlightPath provides otherwise, we may refer to you as a FlightPath client in our marketing materials and other communications. We will not make a press releases shall be made without your written consent.
    4. Business Transfers. FlightPath may share, transfer or sell some or all of its assets, including developer information, in connection with or in anticipation of a corporate event, including a funding, merger, acquisition, sale of stock, recapitalization, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 
  6. ### Changing Your Information

You may review and update your account information by changing your account settings at [link]. 
  7. ### Security

FlightPath uses reasonable measures and security designed to protect developer information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. These measures include encrypting sensitive information using a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and storing information behind a firewall. However, FlightPath cannot ensure, guarantee or warrant the security of all information held, especially against third party attacks or intrusions. Therefore all information provided to FlightPath is provided at the developer risk. 
  8. ### Transfer of Information to United States and Elsewhere

FlightPath stores and processes your information on computers located in the United States and and may also store and process user information in other countries outside the European Union. By using the Services, you expressly consent to the transfer of the information described in this Privacy Policy to the United States and other countries within and outside the EU, and to the application of the laws of the United States. 
  9. ### Our Policy Toward Children

The Website and our Services are not intended for children under 18 years of age and we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If you are aware that a child under 18 has signed up for a developer account or that a child under 13 is using an app that uses FlightPath or has provided us with information in some other way, please contact us at privacy@flightpathapp.com. 
  10. ### California Residents

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, also known as the “Shine the Light Law,” users who are California residents are entitled to request and receive once a year, free of charge, a notice from us describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared, the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, and their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the contact address below. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response. 

* * *

###  Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@testflightapp.com or privacy@flightpathapp.com. 

**TestFlight App, Inc., a subsidiary of Burstly, Inc.**  
1540 2nd Street, 3rd Floor  
Santa Monica CA 90401  
USA

support@testflightapp.com 

Updated: March 22, 2013

This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time, with or without notice to you. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for any amendments or changes
